<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Jurassic Rimworld (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.JurassicRimworld</packageId>
  <author>Serpyderpy</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/JurassicRimworld</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <incompatibleWith>
    <li>Mlie.JurassicRimworldDinosaursOnly</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Serpyderpys mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1419618659

- Patch by asavikle, lower the amount of traders from this mod: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2813022846

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/JurassicRimworld][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/6KqTKks.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Life finds a way.

Jurassic Rimworld brings the wonder and excitement of dinosaurs from the hit franchise right into the chaos of colony management. Hunt or be hunted, breed your own dinosaurs, create your own park, or unleash prehistoric fury on your enemies. The possibilities are endless!

Features include:
- Over one hundred prehistoric creatures, including dinosaurs, pterosaurs, synapsids, invertebrates and many more.
- Large and medium creatures can be used as pack animals, to travel in style!
- Buildings, turrets, walls and floors to decorate in jurassic style and secure your base from dinosaur (or raider) attacks.
- Mineable amber, extraction benches and DNA reconstructing to bring your own creatures back from the past.
- Mod options! Want them to spawn only in the wild? Want to be able to make them yourself? Go nuts!
- Unique sounds and music!
- Much, much more!

Please note this isn't just 'another animal' mod, it makes the game a bit harder, especially at the start! Dinosaurs do spawn in the wild, but you have the option to reconstruct them, as reconstructed dinosaurs are easier to tame and train, with the exception of the Indominus species. Please keep that in mind when downloading.

An extremely big thank you to: Mehni, Lanilor, Shotty, Flake, JayFoxley, Jules, SoggyNoodle, my wonderful Twerp, and everyone else who helped contribute to the mod and kept me going. Thank you so, so much.

Able to be added to current saves.

Compatible with Dinosauria and Megafauna.

Got bug reports, want to suggest a feature for the mod? Hop on over to the discord! Have fun! https://discord.gg/3GeZZq5

KNOWN ISSUES:
If you are having issues with certain buildings not appearing upon constructing the blueprint, please move this mod to the top of your load order underneath Core and Hugslib if you have it. Thank you to NineCities for finding this solution.

If your colonists try to create DNA/Eggs and get stuck at the workbench with the progress bar absent, draft and undraft them. This should fix the problem.

RECOMMENDED MODS:
- Any embrasure mod, to fend off hungry carnivores. I like ED-Embrasures myself!

- Quarry. You will run out of amber to mine eventually, this mod is a huge sigh of relief on that front.

- Cyber fauna. Automatically patches for animals using vanilla body defs, meaning you can give your dinosaurs some sweet mechanical parts without the need for any additional patches!

1.0 MANUAL DOWNLOAD:
https://drive.google.com/file/d/1yQNiCI2WVksGlA-aGH7P4jvk9xODKsrl/view?usp=sharing

DINOSAUR ONLY VERSION:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1804979738

CHINESE TRANSLATION:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1903105216

You are free to use any of the code in this mod as a base, a launchpad, etc.
Do NOT use any of the art in this mod in other mods without my permission. Thank you.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2567489721][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/JurassicRimworld?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url]</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.1</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>